# Zidni Ilmansyah Kadir

Jl.Delima raya no 108 Perumnas 1 Kranji Bekasi Barat

Zidnikadir@gmail.com

+6281382269499

Nationality : Indonesia D.O.B : 21 May 1991

Gender: Male

Marital Statue : Single Religion : Moslem



# **Objective**

To make best use of my knowledge and experience towards achievement of personal as well as organizational goal. At the same time to add value to myself by learning while working and utilizing the same to get the height of career. An energetic and self-motivated.

# **Career Highlights**

### > Rumah Yi as Owner since July 2015 – Present

Import, Selling and Rent Xiaomi Yi. Now Rumah Yi open in Jakarta, Bekasi and Bandung

Company website: www.rumahyi.com

#### **Key Responsbilities:**

- Making brand website and design content the website
- Making sales with dummy blogspot marketing and find new clients
- Manage all recruitment, performance and employee development process
- Manages financial
- Manages design, marketing, promotion, delivery and quality of programs, products and services
- Evaluate and advise on the impact of long range planning, introduction of new programs/strategies and regulatory action
- Maintaining awareness of both the external and internal competitive landscape, opportunities for expansion, customers, markets

#### ➤ Mister Delivery as Owner since August 2014 - Mei 2015

Mister Delivery is 1-2 hours courier service express that provide pickup service to your home/office and directly delivered to client address desired

**Company website**: http://bit.ly/misterdelivery

#### **Key Responsbilities:**

- Making brand website and design content the website
- Making sales with dummy blogspot marketing and find new clients
- Manage all recruitment, performance and employee development process
- Manages financial

#### ➤ Nesindo Energy as HR Coordinator since December 2013 to August 2014

Nesindo energy is general contractor & general suppliers company that focus in civil engineering, architecture, interior design & build, mechanical & electrical, plumbing, infrastructure, casing & pipe Supply, consumable supply, quarry Plant and also man power service.

Company website: www.nesindogroup.co.id

## **Key Responsbilities:**

- Developing HR plans and policies in conjunction with the company over all development plan
- Responsibility of man power planning and recruitments
- Conducting researches to study the current compensation trends in the market
- Co-ordinating with accounting department for processing of payments to employee
- Establishing a proper organizational structure
- Developing and implementing disciplinary policies
- Facilitate the exit process for on time payment of Full & Final settlement

#### ➤ Indo Kaya Energy as HR Staff since August 2013 to December 2013

PT. Indo Kaya Energi is Indonesian OCTG (Oil Country Tubular Goods) company, which one of the branch location in Batam. IKE Batam fabrication supplies Casing / Conductor Pipes for Drilling. It is also supplies many type and size of Threaded Connector / Coupling for Oil & Gas Industries.

Company website: www.indokayaenergi.com

#### **Key Responsbilities:**

- Conducting & co-ordinating interviews.
- Sourcing profiles from the portals and posting vacancies.
- Maintaining daily tracker of candidates interviewed with their complete credentials, status and the source (vendors/employee referrals/Ad walk ins/Job Fairs)
- Job Offer & Appointment Letter
- Payroll function checking accuracy in calculation of salaries and timely disbursement

## **Internship**

- Internhip at Maqdir Ismail & Partner Law Firm, handling transcripts PT.Chevron Pacific Indonesia case bioremediation, from January 2013 – Mei 2013

- Intersnhip at John Fredrick Hengzt & Partner Law Firm, handling export import case, from Juni 2012 – December 2012

# **Achievements**

- Lean Startup Machine Champion
- Certificate IO 9001 Quality Management
- Relocate and promotion to the high HR position
- Implemented the PDCA circle in company

# **Educational Qualification**

Bachelor of Law from University Al-Azhar Indonesia with GPA 3,27 in 2013